Guide to the Duke Photography Faculty and Staff Photographs, circa 1960s-2003 UA.12.03.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Faculty and Staff Photographs, 1
  - Crater, Suzanne, 363
    - Photographs (Box 5)
  - Crawford, Larry, 364
    - Photographs (Box 5)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Crenshaw, James, 365
    - Photographs (Box 5)
  - Crewey, Carla, 366
    - Photographs (Box 5)
  - Cross, Kelly, 367
    - Photographs (Box 5)
  - Crouch, Mary Ann, 368
    - Photographs (Box 5)
  - Crouch, Rebecca, 369
    - Photographs (Box 5)
  - Crowley, James, 370
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Crowley, Thomas, 371
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Crumbliss, Alvin, 372
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Cuccaro, Mike, 373
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Culberson, Bill, 374
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Cullen, Bryan, 375
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Culp, Jerome, 376
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Cummer, Steven, 377
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Curry, Bryan, 378
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dail, Charmane, 379
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dailey, John, 380
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Daley, Shannon, 381
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - D'Amico, Thomas, 382
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Dancy, John, 383
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Daniel, Keith, 384
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Daniels, Donna, 385
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Danner, Richard, 386
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Davidson, Cathy, 387
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Davidson, Clint, 388
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Davidson, Harry, 389
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - CDs (Box 25)
  - Davies, William D., 390
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Davis, Ellen, 391
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Davis, Gregson, 392
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Davis, Jennifer, 393
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Davis, Munsie, 394
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dawkins, Johnny, 395
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dawkins, Kemel, 396
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dawson, Jeff, 397
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dawson, Lois, 398
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Day, Ruth, 399
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - De la Madrid, Miguel, 400
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - De la Paz, Monica, 401
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - De Marchi, Neil, 402
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dean, Kim, 403
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dellinger, Walter, 404
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - DeLong, Robert, 405
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Demark, Wendy, 406
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - DeMott, Deborah, 407
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Denman, Susan, 408
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Desai, Preyas, 409
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Desai, Sanjay, 410
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - DeSanctis, Gerardine, 411
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - DeVeaugh-Geiss, Joseph, 412
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dewey, Alan, 413
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dewhirst, Mark, 414
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Di Giulio, Rich, 415
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Diamond, Irving, 416
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dickerson, Janet, 417
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Dittman, David, 418
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dixon, Kathie, 419
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dobbins, Jim, 420
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dodd, Leslie, 421
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Dodds, Sarah, 422
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dodge, Ken, 423
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Dolbow, John, 424
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dole, Elizabeth, 425
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Donahue, Joe, 426
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Donatucci, Craig, 427
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Donelan, William J., 428
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Doraiswamy, Murali, 429
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Doraiswarmy, Murali, 430
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dorfman, Ariel, 431
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Dowbiggin, William, 432
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Dowell, Earl, 433
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Drezner, Mark, 434
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Driscoll, Tim, 435
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - DuFour, Tammy, 436
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Dugelby, Barbara, 437
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Dumas, Bernard, 438
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Dumas, Paul, 439
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Duncan, Greg, 440
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Dunkley, Leon, 441
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Dunlap, Susan, 442
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Dunn, Susan, 443
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Dupree, Nancy, 444
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Durden, Robert, 445
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Duvall, Robert, 446
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Dyba, Chris, 447
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Dyer, Donna, 448
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Dzau, Victor, 449
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Early, Gordon, 450
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Easley, Mark, 451
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - East, Mark, 452
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - East, Peggy, 453
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Eastlick, Beth, 454
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Eastman, Susan, 455
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Eberle, Pam, 456
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Eckert, Debbie, 457
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Edelman, David, 458
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Edelsbrunner, Herbert, 459
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Edinger, Jack, 460
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Efird, James M., 461
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Egger, Helen, 462
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Einstein, Gillian, 463
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Eisenson, Howard, 464
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - el Saadawi, Nawal, 465
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Eldridge, Al, 466
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Elliott, Nathan, 467
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Elliott, W. W., 468
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Ellis, Matt, 469
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Ellis, Rene, 470
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Elson, Mel, 471
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Emory, Frank E., 472
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Endo, Hitomi, 473
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Ennis, Alana, 474
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Epstein, David, 475
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Erickson, Robert, 476
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Erikson, Harold, 477
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Erwin, Bill, 478
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Esperon, Patricia, 479
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Esser, Cary, 480
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Eubanks, Georgann, 481
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Eubanks, Mary, 482
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Euben, Peter, 483
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Evans, Diane, 484
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Evans, Larry, 485
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Evans, Ron, 486
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Everett, Robinson, 487
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Fairfax, Justin, 488
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Falcone, Grace, 489
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Falletta, John, 490
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Fancher, Martha, 491
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Fandray, Jane, 492
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Favretto, Cristina, 493
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Fawver, Rebecca, 494
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Feagin, John, 495
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Feaver, Peter, 496
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Feinglos, Mark, 497
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Feingloss, Mark, 498
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Felker, Clay, 499
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Fellon, Gail, 500
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Felsman, Kirk, 501
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Ferguson, John, 502
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Fernholz, Rosemary, 503
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Ferrard, Grant, 504
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Ferraro, Thomas, 505
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Ferriero, David Sean, 506
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Ferro, Richard, 507
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Fetter, Anna, 508
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Fetter, Bernard, 509
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Few, Kendrick, 510
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Filipek, Eric, 511
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Fineman, Yale, 512
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Fischer, Karla, 513
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Fish, Peter, 514
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fish, Stanley, 515
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fisher, Samuel R., 516
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fiske, Ted, 517
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fitzgerald, Michael C., 518
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fitzpatrick, Kevin, 519
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Flath, Carol, 520
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fleishman, Joel, 521
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Fleming, Helen, 522
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Florence, Paul, 523
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Forbes, Eleanor, 524
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Forbes, Jeffrey, 525
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fouts, Nevin, 526
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fowler, Craig, 527
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Fowler, Vance, 528
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Fowlie, Wallace, 529
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fowlkes, Deborah, 530
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fox, Brad, 531
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fox, Craig, 532
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fox, Faulkner, 533
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Francher, Marsha, 534
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Frank, Carlos, 535
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Franklin, John Hope, 536
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Franz, Kathy, 537
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Franzoni, Linda, 538
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Fraser-Reid, Bert, 539
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Freeman, Brian, 540
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Freemark, Michael, 541
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Frey, Kip, 542
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Frey, Wolfgang, 543
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fridovich, Irwin, 544
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Friedl, Ernestine, 545
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Friedman, Allan, 546
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Friedman, Bonnie, 547
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Friedman, Henry, 548
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Friedman, Morton, 549
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Friedovich, Irwin, 550
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Froeber, Sarah, 551
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Frush, Karen, 552
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Fulkerson, Mary McClintock, 553
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Fulkerson, William, 554
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Fullenkamp, Connel, 555
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Funderburk, Laney, 556
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Futhey, Tracy, 557
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Futreal, Andy, 558
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Gabert, Helen, 559
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gaines, Jane, 560
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Galbraith, Kristi, 561
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gallagher, John, 562
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gallant, Ron, 563
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gambill, Joetta, 564
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gann, Pamela, 565
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Gao, Xi-Ging, 566
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Garcia, Jorge, 567
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Garcia-Blanco, Mariano, 568
    - Negatives (Box 30)
  - Garcia-Johnson, Ronie, 569
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Garrett, William, 570
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Garst, Jennifer, 571
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gates, Melinda, 572
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Gattis, Allen, 573
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gaudet, Tracey, 574
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gaudet, Tracy, 575
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Gauthier, Dan, 576
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Gavin, Henri, 577
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Gelenbe, Erol, 578
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gelpi, Chris, 579
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gentleson, Bruce, 580
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - George, Linda, 581
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gereffi, Gary, 582
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gergen, David, 583
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gibbons, Randi, 584
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Giddings, Paula, 585
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Gigone, Dan, 586
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gilbert, Paula, 587
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Gilboa, Eli, 588
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Giles, Larry, 589
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Gilkeson, Gary, 590
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Gilland, David, 591
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gillham, Nickolas W., 592
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Gilliam, Bryan, 593
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gilliard, Cathy, 594
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gillis, Malcolm, 595
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gilliss, Catherine, 596
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Ginsberg, Brian, 597
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Ginsburg, Geoffrey, 598
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Giraud, Zannie, 599
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Glander, Ken, 600
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Glass, Jeff, 601
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gminski, Mike, 602
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Goesele, Ulrich, 603
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Goestenkors, Gail, 604
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Gold, Deborah, 605
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Goldberg, Jonathan, 606
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Golding, Martin, 607
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Goldner, Leonard, 608
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Goldschmidt, Pascal, 609
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Goldsmith, Fred, 610
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Goldstein, David, 611
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Goldstein, Larry, 612
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Goli, Veeraindar, 613
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Gongs, Ruby, 614
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Goodall, Jane, 615
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Goodwin, Craufurd, 616
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Goodwin, Linda, 617
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Goodwyn, Lawrence, 618
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gopen, George, 619
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gordon, Deirdre, 620
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Goshaw, Al, 621
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Goss, Kristin, 622
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Grabowski, Henry, 623
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gradison, Margaret, 624
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Gradison, Tina, 625
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Graham, Daniel, 626
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Grandin, Greg, 627
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Granger, Christopher, 628
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Grant, Augustus, 629
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Grant, Ruth, 630
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Graves, Tom and Sara, 631
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gravitt, Brooks, 632
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gray, C. Jarrett, 633
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gray, Linda, 634
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Gray, Stephen, 635
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Grayck, Eva, 636
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Green, Bill, 637
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Green, David, 638
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Green, Judith, 639
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Green, Lois Ann, 640
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Green, Monica, 641
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Greenside, Henry, 642
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gregory, Simon, 643
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Grenier, Roger, 644
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Grensing, Linda, 645
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Grichnik, James, 646
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Griffin, Robert, 647
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Griffith, Bill, 648
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Grimes, Joanne, 649
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Grinstaff, Mark, 650
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Grocott, Hilary, 651
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gronke, Paul, 652
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Grosvenor, Gilbert, 653
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Guerry, Robert, 654
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Guettler, Joe, 655
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Guilak, Farshid, 656
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Guttentag, Christoph, 657
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Guyton, John, 658
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Güzeldere, Güven, 659
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Guzzardi, Peter, 660
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Gwyther, Lisa, 661
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Haagen, Paul, 662
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Haarscher, Guy, 663
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Hacohen, Malachi, 664
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Haff, Peter, 665
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Hagen, Per-Otto, 666
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Haglund, Michael, 667
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 31)
  - Hakirevic, Alma, 668
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Hall, Amy Laura, 669
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hall, Kenneth, 670
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hall, Russel P., 671
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Haltom, Allison, 672
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hamer, Alex, 673
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Hamilton, Jay, 674
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - CDs (Box 25)
  - Hamilton, Michael, 675
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hammes, Gordon, 676
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hammond, Charles, 677
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hammond, Sam, 678
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Handelsman, Leonard, 679
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hanes, Barton, 680
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hanks, John, 681
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hanna, Phil, 682
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hannun, Yusuf, 683
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hansen, John, 684
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hardaker, William, 685
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hardin, Paul, 686
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hargis, Amy, 687
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Harkins, Tom, 688
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Harman, Charles, 689
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Harper, Bob, 690
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Harris, Alex, 691
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Harris, Florentene, 692
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Harris, Lee, 693
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Harris, Lindsey, 694
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Harris, Ross, 695
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Harrison, Kevin, 696
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Harshman, Nate, 697
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hart, William D., 698
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hartemink, Alex, 699
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Harvey, Cam, 700
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Harwood, Kerry, 701
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hastings, Shelly, 702
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hathorn, James, 703
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hauser, Elizabeth, 704
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hauser, Michael, 705
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Havighurst, Clark, 706
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Havrilesky, Thomas, 707
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hawkes, Sara, 708
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hawkins, Jane, 709
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hayden, Allison, 710
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Haynes, Barton, 711
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Haynes, Barton (Department of Medicine Photos), 712
    - Photographs, 1997-1998; folder 1 of 2 (Box 10)
    - Photographs, 1997-1998; folder 2 of 2 (Box 10)
  - Haynie, Kerry, 713
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hays, Richard, 714
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - He, You-Wen, 715
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Head, Susan, 716
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Healy, Mary, 717
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Healy, Robert, 718
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Heath, Chip, 719
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Heitzenrater, Richard, 720
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hellinga, Homme, 721
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Henderson, Barry, 722
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Henderson, Gerri, 723
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Henderson, Karla, 724
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Henderson, Marcus, 725
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Henderson, Martha, 726
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Henson, Diane, 727
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Herman, Steve, 728
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Herndon, Warren, 729
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Heron, Duncan, 730
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Herrera, John, 731
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Herrup, Cynthia, 732
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Herzog, Frederick, 733
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Higginbotham, Elaine, 734
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Higgins, Laurence, 735
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Higginson, Irene, 736
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Higgs, Philip, 737
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hill, Nancy, 738
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hillerbrand, Hans, 739
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hillier, Bill, 740
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hinton, David, 741
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hobin, Anne, 742
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hokazaki, Hank, 743
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Holloway, Karla, 744
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Holloway, Russell, 745
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Holmes, Ed, 746
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Holmes, Rudy, 747
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Holsti, Ole, 748
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Honeycutt, Frances, 749
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hong, Guo-Juin, 750
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hooper, Brett, 751
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hoover, Robert, 752
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Hopkins, Consuela, 753
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Horowitz, Donald, 754
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Horowitz, Jonathan, 755
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Howard, Thad, 756
    - Photographs (Box 10)
  - Huber, Joel, 757
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Hubert, Richard and Linda, 758
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Huddart, Steve, 759
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Hueckel, Tomasz, 760
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Hulette, Christine, 761
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Humphries, Leila, 762
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Hunnings, Rena, 763
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Hurst, Steven, 764
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hurwitz, Herb, 765
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Hütter, Reinhard, 766
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Hylander, William, 767
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Hyslop, Jean, 768
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Ideker, Raymond, 769
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Inch, Kelly, 770
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Inglehart, James, 771
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Ischer, Christine, 772
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Israel, Michael, 773
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Israel, Ronen, 774
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Izatt, Joseph, 775
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 32)
  - Jackson, Joe, 776
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jackson, Myrna, 777
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jackson, Robert, 778
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Jacobs, Mary, 779
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jaffe, Stephen, 780
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Jakubs, Deborah, 781
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - James, Everette, 782
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - James, John, 783
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - James, Shan, 784
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - James, Sherman, 785
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jameson, Frederic, 786
    - Photographs, 1986 January (Box 11)
  - Jameson, Fredric, 787
    - Negatives, 1986 January (Box 33)
  - Jannet, Hugues, 788
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jarvis, Erich, 789
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Jefferies, Shavar, 790
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jeffrey, Paul, 791
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Jelen, Doncho, 792
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jenkins, Kimberly, 793
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Jennings, Willie, 794
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jentleson, Bruce W., 795
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Jirtle, Randy, 796
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Johnson, Al, 797
    - Negatives (Box 33)
  - Johnson, David, 798
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Johnson, David, 799
    - Photographs (Box 11)